imepay.com.np 2018-05-17

# IME pay

We at IME pay, a mobile money platform by IME Digital Solution Ltd.,are committed towards protectingprivacy of our customers using policies regarding the collection, usage and disclosure of the information provided by the customer.

Personally identifiable information includes all information to identify an individual user.

#### **Information collection/ what information do we collect?**

Upon registering walletyourself as an Unverified User, and/or to access services, you willonly need to provide your Mobile Number and Full Name.

If you are being enrolled as a Verified User by an agent, a physical form needs to be filled up and submitted at the agent location which in turn is forwarded to us. Personal information collected and held by us may include your name, father’s name, spouse’s name, date of birth, current and previous addresses, mobile phone number, email address, occupation and information contained in the documents used as proof of identity. IME pay collect, store, process following types of sensitive personal information such as password, financial information (including details of bank account details), and physiological information for providing our products, services via Mobile phone and for use of our website.

We may also hold information related to your utilization of our services by the use of our mobile app which may include following

#### **User Camera / Gallery Photo**

This information is used to obtain a locally stored image of the logged in user to be set as Profile Picture within app. None of the profile image is transferred via internet or collected by the server.

#### **Network State and Internet Access**

The application connects to a dedicated API to complete transactions services provided within. It uses these permissions to check if there is any connection to internet as well as to connect to the internet if not connected.

#### **Read Contacts**

The application accesses user’s phone contacts to select a contact so that the phone number of contact could be populated in the IME pay app using which user can choose to recharge airtime balance instead of having to manually type phone number.

#### **User SMS**

App is able to send and received SMS through user’s device to forward transaction request and confirm transaction status respectively whenever there is no internet available. The user bears sent SMS charge based on the tariff of network provider. Receiving SMS is however free of cost to the user.  
Precise Location Permission (non-continuous)  
Certain feature like Agent locator requires access to location service to display nearby agents in the map.

#### **Information usage/ what do we use customer’s information for?**

The information that we collect from you are used in order to;

#### **Verify your identity**

Complete transaction effectively as per your request  
Communicate about changes to our services  
Respond to your queries in relation to service or assistance  
Protect from unauthorized use of the wallet  
Promote and market our products and services which we think could be of interest to you and may benefit you.  
Safeguard against fraud, money laundering, and misuse of account by incorporating necessary identity verification

#### **Disclosure of information**

Your information will be kept confidential and will not be disclosed to other partyexcept required by regulator and/or you agree for the disclosure.

We may keep a log of the activities performed by you and websites by using various internet techniques such as web cookies, server log files, etc. for analytical purposes and for analysis of the amiability of various features on our site. This information may be used to provide you with a better experience with our platform along with evidentiary purposes.

In case you do not provide your information or consent for usage of personal information or later on withdraw your consent for usage of the personal information so collected, IME pay reserves the right to not provide the services or to withdraw the services for which the said information was sought.

#### **Updates and changes to privacy policy**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Any changes on our privacy policywill be revised and the updated date will be posted at the bottom of this page. However, if there is significant change in the policy, we will provide a more prominent notice throughSMS, push notifications,emailetc.You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications time and again.

“Your consent to use IME pay will adhere to above mentioned privacy policy”.
